
let hardGames = {"0":{"question":"000041008000060070000000030000000800005002004000000025000704900706000501892100043","answer":"367941258128563479459278136214635897675892314983417625531784962746329581892156743"},"1":{"question":"500100000000000560700050023210500600000000030097300015020000000005000000908025000","answer":"532146789189237564746859123213574698654918237897362415421783956365491872978625341"},"2":{"question":"002000600345000200000200030003000800000089000000000300000506080568090400004003061","answer":"172438659345961278689275134913752846426389715857614392231546987568197423794823561"},"3":{"question":"908000000020000670060000008200000806000006201000000000000000900090582013000013765","answer":"918267354324158679567349128231795846475836291689421537153674982796582413842913765"},"4":{"question":"000218600003050080008000120000030806006000050800000300000040000600083500907005040","answer":"459218637123657489768394125214539876376821954895476312531942768642783591987165243"},"5":{"question":"000060000230000000070000000120400000006800003089000001300010000561004732092730000","answer":"914263578238547169675198324123459687756821943489376251347612895561984732892735416"},"6":{"question":"051800000000100000008050000003000000005000710700000005010084000000926801090001400","answer":"251837649349162578678459123163795284985243716724618395512384967437926851896571432"},"7":{"question":"000002007006040500780000004023000090507200003000003000300000000060000902005028400","answer":"154392687236847519789156324423561798597284163618973245342719856861435972975628431"},"8":{"question":"000000000100306700000078130000000890050090026000020410040000008005030001070500603","answer":"387142569129356784564978132412763895758491326936825417643217958895634271271589643"},"9":{"question":"050000000000000009600034050020000800000000300090312400000506980006000020907021536","answer":"152689743834275619679134258325467891461958372798312465213546987586793124947821536"},"10":{"question":"004003000030089000780406000010500009065008001000002000000704000000000000043000710","answer":"154273698236189457789456123312547869465398271897612345521734986678921534943865712"},"11":{"question":"600000000024000600089067000003040807006780001090203050000670002000000010000020000","answer":"635492178724138695189567243513946827246785931897213456451679382362854719978321564"},"12":{"question":"000300000003000009000000000000005008050807104709000000530000002067002503940050601","answer":"125349867473568219698271435214635798356897124789124356531486972867912543942753681"},"13":{"question":"500608374000007000700040000003400700400000603000010000030060000000000432970002001","answer":"512698374346127589789345126123456798457289613698713245231864957865971432974532861"},"14":{"question":"000000020000300080000000305003060000400001000095200400500082004086010032040000871","answer":"314578629259346187678129345123465798467891253895237416531782964786914532942653871"},"15":{"question":"000000400000050000089000000000465000065000000000012006321578004500001800070604300","answer":"152386479437159268689247153713465982265893741894712536321578694546931827978624315"},"16":{"question":"000000500000000000000000004123000007450000013000213460002000008075030940900607350","answer":"214376589368459721597821634123564897456798213789213465632945178875132946941687352"},"17":{"question":"700000050000400670000300104000000080000100006008200300000005800000943501965000032","answer":"714862953239451678586397124421536789357189246698274315143625897872943561965718432"},"18":{"question":"000000000000407500050108000000000708305000004097200000030000070002901853008600041","answer":"123596487689437512754128369246315798315789624897264135531842976462971853978653241"},"19":{"question":"000000010005200009070009040003400008006008127000600053000000964004020070001004000","answer":"239547816145286739678139245513472698496358127782691453327815964864923571951764382"},"20":{"question":"008000000030060070000000000000050009006807012800010405020080000783920050040601000","answer":"158472693439568271267193548314256789596847312872319465621785934783924156945631827"},"21":{"question":"001002000204000000000000003023500090000000000008000040012805070007924030005001060","answer":"531472689264389157879156423123547896746298315958613742312865974687924531495731268"},"22":{"question":"000000010000000000000000000000060098400800006600000145501970860040502000970030001","answer":"253786914164293587789145623325461798417859236698327145531974862846512379972638451"},"23":{"question":"000005670005000200600009000002050007456000010000310450500000904000000000900000003","answer":"123485679795136248648279135312654897456798312879312456531827964267943581984561723"},"24":{"question":"000090000000007489070000030000000000000000006090000000020904800063580042980670010","answer":"138496275256317489479258631312865794847129356695743128521934867763581942984672513"},"25":{"question":"030000005020000000000000006000000000007009063600000020300502678802630900965071002","answer":"134267895526918347789345216413726589257489163698153724341592678872634951965871432"},"26":{"question":"010030000230100000600000000000400009006090000098002305040506092875900003900003000","answer":"514238976237169584689754231153487629426395718798612345341576892875921463962843157"},"27":{"question":"009800010000000670000040000010000090400000003800002000001003080004900300080524761","answer":"239867415145239678678145239312456897456798123897312546521673984764981352983524761"},"28":{"question":"000900050000040009600020000000050090000009000000000460001002980560001030087034510","answer":"124963857375148629698725143713456298846219375259387461431572986562891734987634512"},"29":{"question":"000070000000000780070200000203400090050000203000000540302600000000002074000534621","answer":"124875936536149782879263415263458197458791263791326548342617859615982374987534621"},"30":{"question":"000120000000000000000000100004008607300000048700000000000042970602910034809073010","answer":"435126789281397465967584123154238697396751248728469351513842976672915834849673512"},"31":{"question":"000000030000008000000050100300400000006000000000003056500786900801932005000500002","answer":"124679538657318249983254167395467821416825793278193456532786914841932675769541382"},"32":{"question":"000030000034000500600000020000000080000000230000000000000384607786010304900670812","answer":"125436978834297561679158423261543789497861235358729146512384697786912354943675812"},"33":{"question":"000000004000006089570100000003060097007891060000003000030500000042010000080600001","answer":"168329574324756189579148632213465897457891263896273415731582946642917358985634721"},"34":{"question":"006001000020400080000200067200000000365700014090000000001600002000005001000010605","answer":"436871259527469183189253467214596378365728914798134526951647832642385791873912645"},"35":{"question":"000200070006107089080000000003009000000602001090301245002004010000000000000715032","answer":"134298576526137489789456123213549768845672391697381245352964817971823654468715932"},"36":{"question":"800003000003000789060008100004300090000009002090020000000002608000001000080000041","answer":"812793564453216789769458123124365897638179452597824316971542638346981275285637941"},"37":{"question":"007105620000000580000208000003400008000010060000820000000080006070030851000600300","answer":"387145629124369587569278134753496218842517963691823745235781496476932851918654372"},"38":{"question":"000005000000060500570008000120000000456800000090010065000600000000001002907532801","answer":"612345789389167524574298316123756498456829173798413265231684957845971632967532841"},"39":{"question":"034600000156000000700005200312000700000000003000000060521860000043001800000023600","answer":"234617589156289374789345216312456798465798123897132465521864937643971852978523641"},"40":{"question":"060003000023000000580107000000370809000298100098000005000000002000906000000030086","answer":"164523798723489651589167243416375829357298164298614375675841932832956417941732586"},"41":{"question":"000603070006070000009045006023400080465008000800000460502000000000000000000500000","answer":"148623579256179348379845126723416985465298713891357462512964837934782651687531294"},"42":{"question":"900000000024300009060000000010000007050007000000000000341702905072000081090030740","answer":"935124678724368159168975234213456897659817423487293516341782965572649381896531742"},"43":{"question":"004200000000000408700040030010000700400001000098000004601000040000017090975600002","answer":"154238679263179458789546231316492785427851963598763124631925847842317596975684312"},"44":{"question":"000070000020400000678059124000000098300090000000010003001000000007001040800040650","answer":"435172869129468735678359124714623598382795416956814273241536987567981342893247651"},"45":{"question":"706804000000000000480000007204350000000700000000240000002008076000900850978005014","answer":"716824395325197468489563127264351789153789642897246531532418976641972853978635214"},"46":{"question":"000000000200030009000007000020065000456008000000002006300680900060901308000023600","answer":"134259867275836419689147235821365794456798123793412586317684952562971348948523671"},"47":{"question":"000000500100070060500000000000000000000000000897000050030754000702010645945286000","answer":"364128579128975364579463128213547896456891237897632451631754982782319645945286713"},"48":{"question":"000008107045037000000040200002050000400000090600370400000000000003904006000700010","answer":"236598147145237689789146235312459768457681392698372451521863974873914526964725813"},"49":{"question":"000870000120000009600100205004000000050090120090000000001027008060000000080543001","answer":"549872316123456789678139245214365897356798124897214563431627958765981432982543671"},"50":{"question":"000102058000300600000079003010540000000000000080000000040700060070001380000630010","answer":"394162758721385649568479123217543896439816275685927431143798562976251384852634917"},"51":{"question":"500080000020000000000200000210065000050790003098003450001576002060000000070000561","answer":"534681279127349685689257314213465798456798123798123456841576932365912847972834561"},"52":{"question":"000000005000000300008070100000050000400890003700003050370000902002980037800002041","answer":"123648795547129368968375124231456879456897213789213456374561982612984537895732641"},"53":{"question":"000508010040000000078100000300400000000091000007360001520600073000905100904010060","answer":"239548617145276389678139524312457896456891732897362451521684973763925148984713265"},"54":{"question":"350207000000360009000400020000506098000000005000023000001000000040905002000100600","answer":"354297186127368549689451327213546798468719235975823461531682974746935812892174653"},"55":{"question":"300004060020006080009000034000400890000080100000013400000500000042097000070030602","answer":"358924761421376589769158234217465893534289176896713425683542917142697358975831642"},"56":{"question":"000004100000200500000030040000056790000008002000300005000000820600070000847900651","answer":"235684179469217583178539246324156798591748362786392415913465827652871934847923651"},"57":{"question":"000200000020000000470030000000005890300009000000024000001000070700900000902573604","answer":"135296487628457931479138256214765893356819742897324165541682379763941528982573614"},"58":{"question":"040000000000450680000009045000000790006790000000010000000800050000900870897532060","answer":"145286937729453681368179245451328796286794513973615428612847359534961872897532164"},"59":{"question":"072003000000050000060008003000500000056000017700002000000800974080024000000700802","answer":"172463589348957126569218743213576498856349217794182635621835974987624351435791862"},"60":{"question":"800000001020306000570100000200400800050090300000000104000002005000000000002570613","answer":"834257961129346578576189432217435896458691327693728154341962785765813249982574613"},"61":{"question":"000000048300020000000000003000040090400801000000070000000000981700985302900002700","answer":"125397648346128579879456123261543897497861235538279416652734981714985362983612754"},"62":{"question":"260100003005008000009000000300460090000009000698020000500000080000970002900082001","answer":"264195873135748269789236145352461798417859326698327514523614987841973652976582431"},"63":{"question":"000004000000068070000000004200070800400000000000020105001006902806002701070500060","answer":"127354689594168273638297514213475896465819327789623145341786952856942731972531468"},"64":{"question":"000000000000060500569000100000006709007001200800720005000080007070003801080007423","answer":"123458976748169532569372148214536789357891264896724315431285697672943851985617423"},"65":{"question":"704000050000000000000060004200300000040000000890100040030000587000514000050800401","answer":"714238659326495178589761234267349815145687392893152746431926587678514923952873461"},"66":{"question":"000200000023070000000000125000005090065000000080100000001080900040051080897020051","answer":"456218379123579468978346125214735896365894217789162534531687942642951783897423651"},"67":{"question":"000300052003000000000279106000030000000890200700020005501486000000002000800000001","answer":"167348952293165478458279136612537849345891267789624315521486793936712584874953621"},"68":{"question":"800002000000006000000070100003000600000000007708010005341005906600034800005700402","answer":"814352769237196584569478123123547698456289317798613245341825976672934851985761432"},"69":{"question":"000500900100000008000000006000050080007890000690070000001700090000010820982605410","answer":"234568971156927348879341256413256789527893164698174532341782695765419823982635417"},"70":{"question":"006000400000007009570000003003000700000000006089013050041000060705001000892070500","answer":"916238475234157689578469123123546798457892316689713254341925867765381942892674531"},"71":{"question":"006030000103050700000109000000000007000090100000010000030602000640980205890503001","answer":"926738514183254769475169382314826957258397146769415823531672498647981235892543671"},"72":{"question":"900000008000000000600000000000000000000000283700600415002000047014000062800942500","answer":"921354678435768129678219354243581796156497283789623415592136847314875962867942531"},"73":{"question":"080000076100400000007080004200006790300700025000020001000000000702000800856003012","answer":"584139276123467589967285134215346798348791625679528341431852967792614853856973412"},"74":{"question":"010000050000008600000000004100400890000000210000000000231000006004090002070032501","answer":"312649758457218639698357124163425897849763215725981463231574986584196372976832541"},"75":{"question":"009028000100000000070009000210000800006000020090000000000002970042981050005073402","answer":"369128547124735689578469231217356894456897123893214765631542978742981356985673412"},"76":{"question":"000000300000047009000008100123005006000280000000000000002000068004021000957836240","answer":"461592387238147659579368124123475896746289513895613472312754968684921735957836241"},"77":{"question":"508000010000000070070000060000350097306080020000000005602000001085690040001000750","answer":"528467319163925478479138562214356897356789124897214635642573981785691243931842756"},"78":{"question":"000000240000000070000200008200065007000001006600000015000006002702580961006102030","answer":"137658249528419673469237158214865397875391426693724815351946782742583961986172534"},"79":{"question":"000830400000160009070059103003006000005090000700010005000000074090000000040000006","answer":"159832467234167589678459123913526748425798631786314295361285974597643812842971356"},"80":{"question":"500069004100000080000008007000000800000801402000620000000002000701080023900540700","answer":"528769134137254689469318257213495876675831492894627315356172948741986523982543761"},"81":{"question":"490201600100460009678000000000030008006790000700000300030000900002070010040005030","answer":"495281673123467589678359124214536798356798241789124356531842967862973415947615832"},"82":{"question":"070000030030060079000040125002050700000000010700000500020000080007000300040002600","answer":"174295836235168479689347125312856794456973218798421563521634987867519342943782651"},"83":{"question":"207000090130000500009000000302040709000708230700000605500004000040900002970600000","answer":"257136498134289567689457123362541789495768231718392645523814976846975312971623854"},"84":{"question":"000000800000000000000100030000000060006800307000200050001502006002091500905603100","answer":"123456879457938612869127435514379268296815347738264951381542796642791583975683124"},"85":{"question":"005090208000000509000200030013000096000000020090023400300080052000900700000030640","answer":"135496278427318569689275134213754896854169327796823415341687952562941783978532641"},"86":{"question":"000000000000060080400000000204000008000009010090471230501002906006050800000006543","answer":"162398457379564182485127369214635798753289614698471235531842976946753821827916543"},"87":{"question":"000000000030050000000400100300546080450000236690000005700000090001005007000000002","answer":"124367958839152674576489123312546789457891236698273415743628591261935847985714362"},"88":{"question":"500000000000000000009006040000000007000009000600700053320600900861900532970500801","answer":"512493786436857129789126345143285697257369418698741253325618974861974532974532861"},"89":{"question":"704800091000400070000027040200000000040000000097000000030500960000904013908030500","answer":"724853691153469278689127345215346789346798152897215436431582967562974813978631524"},"90":{"question":"000020000000000000080047000003006790000700200000010006300600900002504300974030650","answer":"135928467427165839689347125213456798546789213798213546351672984862594371974831652"},"91":{"question":"006000000020000070000008000000000789000000402698000153000000000005000024902670300","answer":"136257948824139576759468231243516789517893462698742153461325897375981624982674315"},"92":{"question":"000060500100000600000000007012400096006190200009023015000734000070010300900000001","answer":"237861549145279683698345127312457896756198234489623715521734968874916352963582471"},"93":{"question":"080001000003000000000000060010300008005009010007104300538000004601000025902045030","answer":"286531749193467582754298163419376258365829417827154396538912674641783925972645831"},"94":{"question":"000000900100000000609100000000460789000000003000000450520070690000020370976000000","answer":"234586917157293846689147532312465789495718263768932451523871694841629375976354128"},"95":{"question":"090000005020000000000009204200307000000000010709001000000005900608070021070600800","answer":"193246785425738169867159234214367598586492317739581642341825976658973421972614853"},"96":{"question":"900000000030100089608300005020005800000000000000210056000000000040900301000631500","answer":"912458637435167289678329145126745893753896412894213756361574928547982361289631574"},"97":{"question":"000000000104307080600000000000405008000708000000003546000070960042000851006014000","answer":"235681479194357682678249135361425798459768213827193546513872964742936851986514327"},"98":{"question":"001600800050000200000030050000456790005000000897002005502003074000000080000500620","answer":"231675849456189237789234156123456798645798312897312465512863974364927581978541623"},"99":{"question":"001000050000080000009000020100050780047000200000070005000760004800000002904532871","answer":"381426957726985143459317628132654789547891236698273415213768594875149362964532871"},"100":{"question":"080060000020000680009000000203000090000200000000000400000024000002501000940036521","answer":"184362759325179684679458213213645897496287135857913462531824976762591348948736521"},"101":{"question":"900000640100000009450000020000600790000700200008004350000000900002901835009200060","answer":"923517648186342579457869123231658794564793281798124356375486912642971835819235467"},"102":{"question":"000208004020000000008060200010000000000090000009020300501002900007900500090010043","answer":"135278694426139758978564231213657489754893126869421375541382967387946512692715843"},"103":{"question":"940000008000008400070000000100000090000090031000200040002004960004030002000620314","answer":"941352678236178459578469123123546897465897231789213546312784965654931782897625314"},"104":{"question":"000600000040100260000000005000006000400090000700012450002860000860073020900520040","answer":"125637894348159267697248315251486739436795182789312456512864973864973521973521648"},"105":{"question":"830100070020070000070000004000000009407001300698703000300580000000000003005037240","answer":"834125976126479835579368124213846759457291368698753412341582697762914583985637241"},"106":{"question":"000105007000007000560489023000046008056000000000000000001850070600000000900000050","answer":"234165897189237465567489123712546938456398712893712546321854679645973281978621354"},"107":{"question":"000080000000300000000000030003070869400801000090600400040008900860032741001000203","answer":"134285697587369124629147538213574869456891372798623415342718956865932741971456283"},"108":{"question":"700004000200008000000200004003000960000800327800620415000900700600700500900006000","answer":"715364289246598173389217654423175968561849327897623415158932746634781592972456831"},"109":{"question":"000000000000007000450038000200000008000790005000800010000602974042970000976140020","answer":"123469587689517432457238169214356798368791245795824316531682974842973651976145823"},"110":{"question":"910000000030000070000009000000040000000800001700200000301782965672900004005000702","answer":"914327586236158479587469123128546397469873251753291648341782965672915834895634712"},"111":{"question":"000000003003450609000000008000000000000780100090005000000060982050902760960070530","answer":"145698273283457619679123458516349827324786195798215346437561982851932764962874531"},"112":{"question":"600040090000000000000000000100065000050098000800010050012500060500070021970000345","answer":"621347598345981276789652134134265789256798413897413652412539867563874921978126345"},"113":{"question":"001705000200000060000000000000007080000008300800013004318002040000004008004801532","answer":"461725893235189467789346125123457689546298371897613254318572946652934718974861532"},"114":{"question":"000000008100008000008000000010000800000000006080020305500647080040985631096002050","answer":"253164798164798523978253164319576842425831976687429315531647289742985631896312457"},"115":{"question":"000000000000050700008009000013000090400090062890703410002510070780000000941000003","answer":"124376589369158724578249136213465897457891362896723415632514978785932641941687253"},"116":{"question":"501009008000030500700400020100007000000001007000000000012005004804000000070820301","answer":"521679438468132579739458126143287695685391247297546813312765984854913762976824351"},"117":{"question":"000000000000000000000009000000000008005090000789124000031806002040003050008052031","answer":"123465789497381625856279314264537198315698247789124563531846972942713856678952431"},"118":{"question":"900000170020000089500100000000300090007090410009004050005000900000083500091000700","answer":"943268175126457389578139246452316897637895412819724653285671934764983521391542768"},"119":{"question":"007000000000000000600037000002400708000090002005380104021004030000006007976500480","answer":"137658249258149673649237815312465798864791352795382164521874936483916527976523481"},"120":{"question":"010000000200000000000060000000056700000800000008000010000080090700040050985612347","answer":"314275689256198473879364125192456738537821964468739512643587291721943856985612347"},"121":{"question":"000010000040000000000007000300000000450000238000000500000900846803020051960085002","answer":"235416789147398625689257413398542167451769238726831594512973846873624951964185372"},"122":{"question":"080301000000000000000080000302000090456700000090003000601000005000910000940075012","answer":"284351679137269584569487123312546798456798231798123456671832945825914367943675812"},"123":{"question":"000020800000000079050070200000035000060000000000001060500000940802950000906000083","answer":"173429856284563179659178234421635798365897421798241365517386942832954617946712583"},"124":{"question":"000000210000350009008000300000005000000090700700030154030600000840003000900007001","answer":"354769218172358469698124375413875692265491783789236154531682947847913526926547831"},"125":{"question":"300040000100000008009000000003006009007800023090000450000080030000012560904073012","answer":"325748691176259348489361275513426789647895123892137456251684937738912564964573812"},"126":{"question":"000000900020450000089007000004000060000000400897000051000000000560090030071020580","answer":"135268947726459318489137625214975863653812479897346251342581796568794132971623584"},"127":{"question":"005060000000000009070000000200000000000080007798604013501042968800506700900000004","answer":"145369872682175349379428156216937485453281697798654213531742968824596731967813524"},"128":{"question":"030010000000600009000349005200050007000000000800003450000700080702000501980001060","answer":"439215678125678349678349125213456897546897213897123456351762984762984531984531762"},"129":{"question":"200005000000008079670039000000056800000000003000020000000073004030902516000500030","answer":"219745368345168279678239145193456827762891453854327691521673984437982516986514732"},"130":{"question":"000310600000000080068009100000000000300000007089000010000000908095002403872040000","answer":"247318659913256784568479132124537896356891247789624315431765928695182473872943561"},"131":{"question":"000000000000000500600000000000470000000000002790600415305002046000900750007001823","answer":"134856297278319564659247138521473689486195372793628415315782946862934751947561823"},"132":{"question":"000000000100079060000108000000400000056800120000013400600000090000961042900500600","answer":"237645819184379265569128734312456978456897123798213456623784591875961342941532687"},"133":{"question":"000000200004000700000009030003000000000000312008003400001002900805010623902600571","answer":"136457289294381756587269134423195867759846312618723495361572948875914623942638571"},"134":{"question":"000070000000000479608000020100400000000890030700200500000000080007080000890031654","answer":"914372865235168479678549123123456798456897231789213546341625987567984312892731654"},"135":{"question":"900000400000000070400000000204056000000000000009010050000000000640082735802730600","answer":"913527468526148379478693521234856197165279843789314256357461982641982735892735614"},"136":{"question":"000000000100000009000089200214035090005000600000000300530000902000900001000002543","answer":"629347158178526439453189276214635897395278614786491325531764982842953761967812543"},"137":{"question":"004900008000060000009000124010030090040000010000020000000006000502801703070243600","answer":"724915368138462975659378124216534897347689512985127436493756281562891743871243659"},"138":{"question":"001000800000078000080000000000000000000890003090320010302704905870000000904580070","answer":"231459867456178239789236154123645798647891523598327416312764985875913642964582371"},"139":{"question":"000000000004000000000106000000000008006700020800213050531670900000594000002030000","answer":"123457896674389512985126473217965348356748129849213657531672984768594231492831765"},"140":{"question":"008000000000000000050000008000350000007001000009020300600080905040010602002564701","answer":"128436579496875213753192468264358197537941826819627354671283945345719682982564731"},"141":{"question":"300020050100000400780000000203040089000100072007060000501800200048900030000005001","answer":"364721958125389467789456123213547689456198372897263514531874296648912735972635841"},"142":{"question":"005000000100050080000100206000300800050001020009720030000000978040080001806007302","answer":"235678419164259783978134256612345897357891624489726135521463978743982561896517342"},"143":{"question":"009000300005068470000000005000000800506000000090000500000070000000004650964580702","answer":"149257368235168479678349125412735896586491237793826541351672984827914653964583712"},"144":{"question":"000000000000000000600340025200000798000890006800000514001600900000000850038075602","answer":"124567389359218467687349125213456798475891236896723514541682973762934851938175642"},"145":{"question":"000090004000050000000000000200400000050000020900003001340002900000934670700080503","answer":"125396784438157269679248135213465897854719326967823451346572918581934672792681543"},"146":{"question":"009100000000000000400009106000060890060800000095004060030002970000010000900080610","answer":"259136487176428359483759126714265893362891745895374261531642978628917534947583612"},"147":{"question":"009060008130000000600100200002000000000090307000000100500000703060002001900007052","answer":"249763518135248679678159234312475896456891327897326145521984763764532981983617452"},"148":{"question":"007020041020000000000000236004000000065007004098000000001600000800900002042080050","answer":"387526941426139578519478236134265897265897314798314625951642783873951462642783159"},"149":{"question":"000000028000000000000006040103060800450000013800010000048000062062800000070020500","answer":"614357928239148657785296341193462875456789213827513496548931762962875134371624589"},"150":{"question":"000000000023000078400208030000000000305090000000104005001000940002043050040010020","answer":"158379264923461578467258139214835697385697412796124385531782946672943851849516723"},"151":{"question":"080000200000108060500000000100000806006890000700026005000600000000015983800930620","answer":"381469257247158369569273148132547896456891732798326415913682574624715983875934621"},"152":{"question":"030000000005000000009050004000400090000001000090270140040086900060004083070030001","answer":"134627859685149237729358614213465798457891326896273145341586972962714583578932461"},"153":{"question":"000081300004000000000000000200465000000000000089020000320670000040902000060010432","answer":"592781346134256789678349125213465897456897213789123564321674958845932671967518432"},"154":{"question":"090002100024057009500009000003000000007600000000003050000000000040930000902781043","answer":"396842175124357689578169234213475896457698312689213457731524968845936721962781543"},"155":{"question":"650039800003408560700050100000000000300000200000002000400700080002000003078610402","answer":"654139827123478569789256134215347698346891275897562341431725986562984713978613452"},"156":{"question":"070040000000060000000008000000000009000097210007004300031000047005416903942080060","answer":"173245698829361475564978132416832759358697214297154386631529847785416923942783561"},"157":{"question":"700000000004100000060200170000050007400008002870002000000807940040000780907000001","answer":"712384569594176238368295174236451897459768312871932456623817945145629783987543621"},"158":{"question":"004007000120000789700000000203000007050000030000000054502090860001002075070061000","answer":"364987512125346789789125346213458697456279138897613254532794861641832975978561423"},"159":{"question":"080005400000060080000000026023400090000000001700210005300500000000600050005870310","answer":"286135479457962183931748526123456798569387241748219635372591864814623957695874312"},"160":{"question":"040012000003050000070000000000006000000090000800004000431085060702040803005600402","answer":"546312789193758246278469135317826594654197328829534671431285967762941853985673412"},"161":{"question":"080090000000400000570000000005040000300000020700000030431020090850070000060014300","answer":"182596473693487152574132869925348617318769524746251938431825796859673241267914385"},"162":{"question":"000900000000000670009340100012060000000080003090003546500030984643000050070000000","answer":"156972438234158679789346125312465897465789213897213546521637984643891752978524361"},"163":{"question":"001800900035070400700000000020000080506008000090000050000500006600901543004003020","answer":"241835967835679412769214835427156389516398274398427651183542796672981543954763128"},"164":{"question":"004060800000000009000300000010005008056000000709600050000904080043000091067001203","answer":"134269875275148639698357124312475968456892317789613452521934786843726591967581243"},"165":{"question":"000000000023000009008000000000005800050090010890004060030072058005080400902003000","answer":"149236587523817649678459231314765892256398714897124365431672958765981423982543176"},"166":{"question":"007004000000000070000257004003000000400000007700000000000940702064020001070080306","answer":"127364589645198273389257164253479618416835927798612435831946752564723891972581346"},"167":{"question":"000000600000067000067009130010000700000000203000000450341800960000030001800001320","answer":"124358697938167542567249138413526789659784213782913456341872965296435871875691324"},"168":{"question":"500084003000000078000123000004000000057090000080000230700000082840000006905000041","answer":"519784623423569178678123495294318567357296814186457239731645982842931756965872341"},"169":{"question":"000002000100000000000100205204030700000000100090000050000040000041920007005870023","answer":"356482971127359648489167235214538796573296184698714352732645819841923567965871423"},"170":{"question":"050000006100050000400008005200037600300009014000004000007002901000015000900703000","answer":"752391486183456279469278135214537698378629514695184327537842961826915743941763852"},"171":{"question":"007800000000050000000470000210500600000100000700000000041680970000904800000012306","answer":"127863459436259187589471263213547698895126734764398521341685972672934815958712346"},"172":{"question":"000000064005000000000007000000050700000098002090310000030075801578920043901004000","answer":"217583964345269178689147325823456719156798432794312586432675891578921643961834257"},"173":{"question":"390210070000608000000040000000450000000090003009003450530000984007000560900004001","answer":"394215678125678349678349125213456897456897213789123456531762984847931562962584731"},"174":{"question":"000000000000000000000039260000000807300000105570004020001500004702003601890001730","answer":"123468579968257413457139268216395847384726195579814326631572984742983651895641732"},"175":{"question":"000200000100070000579000003000040000007000036000700400000000807062084051080030042","answer":"436215789128379564579468123691843275847521936253796418314652897762984351985137642"},"176":{"question":"080000000000000080400200005200300090006700412708004050531000060600001000040900501","answer":"182457639975613284463289175214365798356798412798124356531842967629571843847936521"},"177":{"question":"060100500030040000789050020000060000407800000000000405501000780003670050006500040","answer":"264187539135249678789356124312465897457891263698723415521934786843672951976518342"},"178":{"question":"040000000030000009000007000200450060006000000800002054024010000000900006901870503","answer":"142369785637185249598247631219458367456731892873692154324516978785923416961874523"},"179":{"question":"000000075000000080000045000100006000000009003098000254001590007000031942004070500","answer":"213968475456127389789345126132456798547289613698713254321594867875631942964872531"},"180":{"question":"000001000103000000070300000000630700006000215080005063000706902050000000900000301","answer":"248961537193457826675328149521634798436879215789215463314786952852193674967542381"},"181":{"question":"000002070004050000508000000003070800050600000080013000000520000045936701900700503","answer":"136842975274159386598367142623475819451698237789213654367521498845936721912784563"},"182":{"question":"060000310130000009000000200310065090000000100000002006000000004073941000948023060","answer":"264759318135284679789136245312465897456897123897312456521678934673941582948523761"},"183":{"question":"007009000020000000000000000000006097005002046008017005000760000702900650006200700","answer":"137529468524638971689174532241356897375892146968417325453761289712983654896245713"},"184":{"question":"200000000130006000060170030000005090000789010008000400000043000000097500905000640","answer":"254938167137256984869174235312465798546789312798312456621543879483697521975821643"},"185":{"question":"060028000020000089008009005000500090050802000000000050030000000000201960980003500","answer":"569128347123457689478369125812534796657892431394716258236975814745281963981643572"},"186":{"question":"040070902000000008000000030020405080000090010000010060300080000504031020980006041","answer":"641378952235149678798652134123465789456897213879213465312784596564931827987526341"},"187":{"question":"206800050000000600000000020000000060000000200090003540001000085060041790000082300","answer":"216834957457129638389657124142795863635418279798263541921376485863541792574982316"},"188":{"question":"300670000024000000000000000200000890000000000098000060600704000072001040040580703","answer":"315672489724198356869345172236457891157869234498213567683724915572931648941586723"},"189":{"question":"060800002100400500000120060005040000000000020080000600000902056000000080852007000","answer":"364859172128476539579123468215648397643791825987235614431982756796514283852367941"},"190":{"question":"000007050000000070009006000203000807000000320008000000030000082862090740974032000","answer":"126387459345129678789456231213645897457918326698273514531764982862591743974832165"},"191":{"question":"300100900000300500060078000000006000050007200097013450000004000000000045940000307","answer":"324165978178329564569478123213546789456897231897213456631754892782931645945682317"},"192":{"question":"000900103000006709000130000000005000056000302000000050000040070843007600900020530","answer":"285974163134256789679138245312465897456789312798312456521643978843597621967821534"},"193":{"question":"030000120000350070000000000000000006000800007080200050301500900502000080000002513","answer":"435678129126359478798124635213795846654813297987246351341587962562931784879462513"},"194":{"question":"000800100000000000070100006200005007000090201080000060001600900607501002840907000","answer":"324876159156249783978153426213465897465798231789312564531624978697581342842937615"},"195":{"question":"000000000000000000070000020010065090050080200090100405000000070040030950080672314","answer":"123546789568297143479318526312465897654789231897123465231954678746831952985672314"},"196":{"question":"000701300000250009000000100302005006000890000009030005000500000000907500000623080","answer":"294761358136258479578349162312475896457896213689132745921584637863917524745623981"},"197":{"question":"030049060006000070000000030020000090400800006000000000012004957000903040004002000","answer":"135749268246138579789256134521467893493825716678391425312684957857913642964572381"},"198":{"question":"000000000130006000600050000000005090050000000060000050306010978580037002790602500","answer":"245173689138296745679458123412365897853749216967821354326514978581937462794682531"},"199":{"question":"200940800130008500000000000300400090050020000008100000000690083000003062900000001","answer":"275941836134268579689357124312475698456829317798136245521694783847513962963782451"},"200":{"question":"501003000000000000600050000000400700050708000090300006310804090800901073040000001","answer":"521643987473189562689257134136492758254768319798315246312874695865921473947536821"},"201":{"question":"080019000130200080000300104203000090500001006000000000300080900750000060908102000","answer":"482519637137246589695378124213465798579821346846793215324687951751934862968152473"},"202":{"question":"000040000020000000050209000010056807000007000080900300000004701040730900901025000","answer":"136548279429173568758269134213456897594387612687912345362894751845731926971625483"},"203":{"question":"007080000003000700060309100210000890000000070700004050000000008001960507075003402","answer":"127586349593241786468379125216735894354698271789124653632457918841962537975813462"},"204":{"question":"600800000000300009500000300210000000000008123000200004001002008760000000082504070","answer":"623819457147325869598476312214937586975648123836251794451762938769183245382594671"},"205":{"question":"000000090000109560000200000003070600000001203000020405000000050500000020908512346","answer":"124356798387149562659287134213475689845691273796823415432768951561934827978512346"},"206":{"question":"000000002000058070670020008010300006065200047007000200000000700000000900986000023","answer":"158437692392658174674129538219374856865291347437586219543962781721843965986715423"},"207":{"question":"600000005000007600000000130000400000000091000090603451300002900060980503001030740","answer":"612349875435817629879265134126458397543791268798623451354172986267984513981536742"},"208":{"question":"059000401000000000460000000000370090000001020000024070000740000600000710980516042","answer":"259637481173482569468159237812375694734961825596824173321748956645293718987516342"},"209":{"question":"000100000003050700070000100004360000000800000098000000001002008705080002980673500","answer":"246137859813956724579248136124365987657829413398714265431592678765481392982673541"},"210":{"question":"009000006030100070560409023103000000400000000890210000301050900600000054000000002","answer":"719325486234168579568479123123546798456987231897213645341852967682791354975634812"},"211":{"question":"000000600020000080060000020213400000406000200700000400000820000070930042090604501","answer":"134258679527169384968347125213486957456793218789512463341825796675931842892674531"},"212":{"question":"000020000030009000000308020120000700050000000090000400000000065000031840082605017","answer":"415726938238419576679358124126594783854173692793862451341987265567231849982645317"},"213":{"question":"007000200100000700400000000200000000000010002090000305600042908840903000070081504","answer":"357164289126598743489237651231475896568319472794826315615742938842953167973681524"},"214":{"question":"000005200200100780070200000000400008006800007807002000001080900000501800080020500","answer":"138675249245139786679248315352417698496853127817962453521386974764591832983724561"},"215":{"question":"001000000004000500570360000003056000000090000000010050007600985042000000060081042","answer":"231548679684179523579362418123456897458297136796813254317624985842935761965781342"},"216":{"question":"000000600030006009009000000003005000050089030008200006000000000045690070067832504","answer":"172958643534126789689347125213465897456789231798213456321574968845691372967832514"},"217":{"question":"000000000000000070780050000000000000006000012807300005000571000501984703978003501","answer":"123467958659138274784259136215846397346795812897312465432571689561984723978623541"},"218":{"question":"980000000103080007000023080000000000006000000000050000400867002602000870009010004","answer":"984175236123486597567923481241638759356749128798251643435867912612394875879512364"},"219":{"question":"000000000020006000009020005200008000340001008800000000001082006060900803070613400","answer":"153849267724156389689327145215738694346591728897264531531482976462975813978613452"},"220":{"question":"207000003100000009009000240000405000450000000700012000000000908040006520000820300","answer":"267149853134258679589367241312485796456793182798612435623574918841936527975821364"},"221":{"question":"800000000000000080060008004205034090000009005000010460000500000680103500902040600","answer":"813426759427951386569378124275634891146789235398215467731562948684193572952847613"},"222":{"question":"070000060005000080000050004002400807000090210000100400000600008807009030003072000","answer":"174283569235946781689751324312465897458397216796128453521634978847519632963872145"},"223":{"question":"000100000020000009400000056004060090000800000600724010031000000000080020080573601","answer":"365197284827456139419238756174365892253819467698724315531642978746981523982573641"},"224":{"question":"019040800000060000000009000103005600000800000090200000000007900005920003002634700","answer":"319742856254168379678359124123475698547896231896213547431587962765921483982634715"},"225":{"question":"005000000100000000609008000000400689000001030000023400000030800043000052900002341","answer":"235146978184297563679358124312475689458961237796823415521734896843619752967582341"},"226":{"question":"008000003000400060507000100000000897000800000080024000401002900602000000070000601","answer":"148569273293417568567238149324156897716893452985724316431672985652981734879345621"},"227":{"question":"070000003100059000000000000000065000050890000800020060600000097003000000905710302","answer":"274681953138259476569374128312465789456897231897123564641532897723948615985716342"},"228":{"question":"070000000000467009000000100000000000300000000008102000000074062040953800087010403","answer":"273591648815467239469328175126735984354689721798142356931874562642953817587216493"},"229":{"question":"000200040004178069500000023100500000050000001009000400312000000600001000800720600","answer":"961235748234178569578469123123546897456897231789312456312684975647951382895723614"},"230":{"question":"900000400000000780400100200200000000368000500500000063030002070005010000000903051","answer":"923578416156234789487196235219365847368741592574829163631452978895617324742983651"},"231":{"question":"580000000000000070070100008000000000450800320700000000301080900800900030000013580","answer":"582347169194658273673129458239476815456891327718532694361785942825964731947213586"},"232":{"question":"000007092020000008000000130000465780000800003090000000500902040084000001002080007","answer":"138547692426391578759628134213465789645879213897213465571932846384756921962184357"},"233":{"question":"002000100030000000000009000003050807458700062609000000001605080705900600906800000","answer":"592348176134567928867129435213456897458791362679283514341675289785912643926834751"},"234":{"question":"000008000230000080000000005023009600400000390090000450002005060000013027078004010","answer":"145268739239457186687391245823549671451786392796132458312875964564913827978624513"},"235":{"question":"400009000000000000609107000000000000000091000708000001301804926000010070900035014","answer":"412359687537468192689127345143582769265791438798643251351874926824916573976235814"},"236":{"question":"000608010020007009000120000000000700307000100800001004430005000000000040960730501","answer":"543698217126457839789123456614382795357946182892571364431265978275819643968734521"},"237":{"question":"680000000000009000070060105000500080000007000000204300500000900840003561001045800","answer":"682351497135479628479862135214536789396187254758294316563718942847923561921645873"},"238":{"question":"007204000100000670008100000000400006000000000000003401340010980091000042870040060","answer":"537264819124389675968157234283491756419576328756823491342615987691738542875942163"},"239":{"question":"070003000034000000009000030020000000400000003000010050010504968860000042940028001","answer":"172453689534869127689172435721345896456987213398216754217534968863791542945628371"},"240":{"question":"000000200003060580050009007010050000000091000009720010530000970700003850000070031","answer":"146587293973162584258439167317854629625391748489726315531248976764913852892675431"},"241":{"question":"200000000130000000000300100000065890000089060090700000021000630040630900003070010","answer":"254196378136827459789354126372465891415289763698713245921548637547631982863972514"},"242":{"question":"000500800000000000000040005020400700000800000800000456001004970000031004904705630","answer":"132567849465198327798243165523416798647859213819372456351684972276931584984725631"},"243":{"question":"000300020000000000000208104000475809006090000097010052000000000000004000985000041","answer":"148357926263149578579268134312475869456892317897613452624581793731924685985736241"},"244":{"question":"002000000000070000709000020210006008500000003690020000000084675000030000970000300","answer":"132458796456279831789613524217346958548197263693825147321984675865732419974561382"},"245":{"question":"000000807130008009500060003310040000050090300080300204000004000003000902005000400","answer":"246139857137258649598467123312746598654892371789315264921684735463571982875923416"},"246":{"question":"000000000000000009400009000004000790000098210000024300030046070600900020901500003","answer":"129453687863217549475689132214365798356798214798124356532846971647931825981572463"},"247":{"question":"900000400000000500000080006210056000075090000009000005500008907046900000090073641","answer":"923165478168437592457289136214356789375891264689724315531648927746912853892573641"},"248":{"question":"000100020000008000000060004000470806000020010790010000005701980040030050001002063","answer":"357194628426358179189267534213475896564829317798613245635741982842936751971582463"},"249":{"question":"690508300004009000070000000000056890006000000700002000007601000060920000900700010","answer":"691548372234179568578263149312456897456897231789312456847631925163925784925784613"},"250":{"question":"600040800000000000009000120023000000000000007790000002002580706860000500045000281","answer":"631245879258179364479368125123497658584612937796853412312584796867921543945736281"},"251":{"question":"000000500000000009000000000000500000456700231090210056001020907600931000980000302","answer":"123896574765342189849157623217563498456789231398214756531428967672931845984675312"},"252":{"question":"000000000020400000000000008210300000000801000780020035605000004800900502000006013","answer":"143258679928467351567139248214375896356891427789624135635712984871943562492586713"},"253":{"question":"000002350000050009000000000010000000300080100000600520430090000005840902081000400","answer":"147962358263158749859374216514729683326485197798613524432596871675841932981237465"},"254":{"question":"000000020103008000050070006000506807300007004080004300007000000600900003000003041","answer":"469315728173268459258479136924536817315897264786124395537641982641982573892753641"},"255":{"question":"209003008000050000078100200000075000400000000000000400500030084700082003000510700","answer":"259743168146258379378169245631475892425891637897326451512637984764982513983514726"},"256":{"question":"269000001130208000000000206010000000000000100000000460601003900083045000905001300","answer":"269354781137268549458179236314596827876432195592817463621783954783945612945621378"},"257":{"question":"000160000100008009080000100010040090458090000096000000000000980001903000000000061","answer":"234169578165278439987354126312546897458792613796831245523617984641983752879425361"},"258":{"question":"006300000000058600009000034004000000357000000000010020000040002002071063960803410","answer":"176394258423158679589762134214539786357286941698417325731645892842971563965823417"},"259":{"question":"700000000020000009689000000200000097000000010000003000301602050560000002070038600","answer":"713249586425186379689357124236815497857964213194723865341672958568491732972538641"},"260":{"question":"000600000100000400780200030000000000057098300000720500000000075870904000000000841","answer":"234619758165873429789245136428531697657498312913726584346182975871954263592367841"},"261":{"question":"067000000024300000080040000000056090000000000006800410030000704805000901940175080","answer":"167289345524361879389547162413756298798412536256893417631928754875634921942175683"},"262":{"question":"006000100004000000000020000200065000007000000090003400000500060840602901900871500","answer":"326947158174358296589126347213465789457289613698713425731594862845632971962871534"},"263":{"question":"900004000030000000000000000100000000000007000000210456302608910690042070875031002","answer":"916324587238756194457189263124865739563497821789213456342678915691542378875931642"},"264":{"question":"000074000230000000000200030100000000008000003070000005312548976000000300000907021","answer":"561374289234189567789256134145763892628495713973812645312548976497621358856937421"},"265":{"question":"085000000000400080009000000010000000006700020800000006500800900008002015902571803","answer":"185237469623419587479658231214396758396785124857124396541863972738942615962571843"},"266":{"question":"000100000020000009000409000014050800000007200007204000000623905000900741080700600","answer":"349162578126578439758439162214356897563897214897214356471623985632985741985741623"},"267":{"question":"900000000100060000560000000000000008046090015780000300431000907657901002800000000","answer":"923145786174368529568729431219453678346897215785216394431582967657931842892674153"},"268":{"question":"030000005025340600080006000013000000450007010000000406040000007000971340900004001","answer":"634718295125349678789526134813465729456297813297183456341652987568971342972834561"},"269":{"question":"000000096200060000000000023020040000000000001908003200000684007000901632090005010","answer":"134527896279368145856419723521746389743892561968153274312684957485971632697235418"},"270":{"question":"081000070300107200079008000000070000050090307090603001000000008830900002000000000","answer":"281349576345167289679528134163274895452891367798653421516732948834916752927485613"},"271":{"question":"000300000000070000700050023000500800007000200090200700300060902060920007900831600","answer":"124386579539172468786459123213547896457698231698213745341765982865924317972831654"},"272":{"question":"000070090005000000600300020000065009050090200000020006000004007567032800984010000","answer":"123576498475289613698341725241765389856193274739428156312854967567932841984617532"},"273":{"question":"000005200000000000000230005000000897057001020060007000002570000000900730704683000","answer":"136745289528169473479238165241356897857491326963827541392574618685912734714683952"},"274":{"question":"400000050000300060009450003000500008047080000000100000301294006000013005074005300","answer":"413628759285379164769451283132547698647982531598136427351294876826713945974865312"},"275":{"question":"340600010000000000000000040003000097450708000800200056001000900000001080082060000","answer":"345629718127384569698175243213546897456798321879213456561832974734951682982467135"},"276":{"question":"090204070000000000050000200000000708065090120009010060008020907001900002900800003","answer":"193254876246187539857639241312546798765398124489712365638421957571963482924875613"},"277":{"question":"070008000000000480480000060004006708007200000000000000000090800865004920000835070","answer":"172468359356729481489351267234516798597283146618947532743692815865174923921835674"},"278":{"question":"008300000020400000406709003004007098060000000879000305500002000607000000000000501","answer":"198325467723416859456789123214537698365198274879264315531942786647851932982673541"},"279":{"question":"000004000045060078000000000100000009450300000090000300500006003034021007907000020","answer":"216784935345169278789235164173642589452398716698517342521476893834921657967853421"},"280":{"question":"000001000003006000460000020200000000050090007000004013600000000702680900080712406","answer":"527341698893256174461978325238167549154893267976524813615439782742685931389712456"},"281":{"question":"000082000020000000000000030214030000300090010080710002702840000801900000005001020","answer":"143682579529173486678459231214538967357296814986714352762845193831927645495361728"},"282":{"question":"000640000100080000400000080000000008300700024700000000000070040805900276000460850","answer":"238641597157289463469357182594126738381795624726834915612578349845913276973462851"},"283":{"question":"000200004000000570000000000000006000000001000008000415002018953000970001000534820","answer":"156287394234169578879345162315426789497851236628793415742618953583972641961534827"},"284":{"question":"000000070030000080000040035100400700450080000000002006000801007700000040060074023","answer":"214358679537169284698247135126435798459786312873912456342891567785623941961574823"},"285":{"question":"750008930000000000000300004203475000005800010090000000000584701500920003040000800","answer":"751248936324169578986357124213475689465892317897613245632584791578921463149736852"},"286":{"question":"005907000004000080000000040000000000006080000700213000001092070560070030900604500","answer":"185947263324156789697328145813765492256489317749213658431592876562871934978634521"},"287":{"question":"000010000120400000007009020000000708300798000098000000000006072002900603006250000","answer":"435812967129467835687539421261345798354798216798621354943186572512974683876253149"},"288":{"question":"270000001100000000500000200002000000050000000090300000021000050040901080003645012","answer":"274536891138279465569418237312864579456197328897352146621783954745921683983645712"},"289":{"question":"005000604040039500000050100020547000050000000000002400000004000064000750002065001","answer":"135278694246139578789456123321547869458691237697382415513724986864913752972865341"},"290":{"question":"705040002000580067000000100000306700050008200007000000530600000000901000000035640","answer":"765143892123589467489267135214356789356798214897412356531624978648971523972835641"},"291":{"question":"000002037023000080000000000200036000300000000000020350401005002097041800060903410","answer":"145682937623197584789354621258436179376519248914728356431865792597241863862973415"},"292":{"question":"009200000004050700508000000000065007000090000800023000005600900000000502900537641","answer":"139274856264358719578916234321865497456791328897423165715642983643189572982537641"},"293":{"question":"000010064000060009070000005000000090000000200080003006020634087864000002037000040","answer":"253719864148265379679348125312456798496187253785923416921634587864571932537892641"},"294":{"question":"000000070000100008780200000100050000005008000000000050500060000030081527970020060","answer":"213845679456179238789236145142357896365498712897612354521764983634981527978523461"},"295":{"question":"000040070100060000000000005010000700000090040008400000031000067740950010980703020","answer":"253148679179365482864279135415682793327591846698437251531824967742956318986713524"},"296":{"question":"000008000000000000600104000000000006450801703007036000341500007000010084000007000","answer":"123658479574293168689174235932745816456821793817936542341589627765312984298467351"},"297":{"question":"800000502003500000000200000010300080000000010000010060030680947040020801900745020","answer":"864137592123594678579268134412356789396872415758419263235681947647923851981745326"},"298":{"question":"010000032004000080080030100000460800000000000000700005005621000801907000000083610","answer":"516874932234159786789236154123465879457398261698712345375621498861947523942583617"},"299":{"question":"000000000000209560009000003010000000000800030008000456020080000540000807980005002","answer":"132567984874239561659148273315496728467852139298371456721684395546923817983715642"}};

const miniBox1 = document.getElementById('mini-box-1');
miniBox1.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 0) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox2 = document.getElementById('mini-box-2');
miniBox2.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 1) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox3 = document.getElementById('mini-box-3');
miniBox3.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 2) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox4 = document.getElementById('mini-box-4');
miniBox4.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 3) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox5 = document.getElementById('mini-box-5');
miniBox5.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 4) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox6 = document.getElementById('mini-box-6');
miniBox6.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 5) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox7 = document.getElementById('mini-box-7');
miniBox7.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 6) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox8 = document.getElementById('mini-box-8');
miniBox8.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 7) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });
const miniBox9 = document.getElementById('mini-box-9');
miniBox9.addEventListener('click', function (e, num = 8) {
    e.stopPropagation();
    miniBoxMaximize(num);
  });

const allBoxes = [miniBox1, miniBox2, miniBox3, miniBox4, miniBox5, miniBox6, miniBox7, miniBox8, miniBox9];
const allLines = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('line'));

const minimizeVars = ['box1DecreaseSize', 'box2DecreaseSize', 'box3DecreaseSize', 'box4DecreaseSize', 'box5DecreaseSize', 'box6DecreaseSize', 'box7DecreaseSize', 'box8DecreaseSize', 'box9DecreaseSize'];
const maximizeVars = ['box1IncreaseSize', 'box2IncreaseSize', 'box3IncreaseSize', 'box4IncreaseSize', 'box5IncreaseSize', 'box6IncreaseSize', 'box7IncreaseSize', 'box8IncreaseSize', 'box9IncreaseSize'];
let isMaximizedBool = false;

// number of the box thats maximized
let miniBoxOnNumber;

// all maximizable boxes
const allTapBoxes = getReadingOrientationNumbers();

// the game number (0-299)
let GAME_NUMBER = 0;

// the game state
let GAME_STATE = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the original state of board without touching it
let GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];

// the menu button orientation boolean
let isMenuOpen = false;

// gets all 81 boxes in box order and returns them in reading left to right order
function getReadingOrientationNumbers() {
    let temp = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('tap-box'));
    let ret = [];

    let one = 0;
    let two = 9;
    let three = 18;
    for (let i = 0; i < 3; i++) {
        for (let j = 0; j < 3; j++) {
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(one, one + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(two, two + 3));
            Array.prototype.push.apply(ret, temp.slice(three, three + 3));
            one = one + 3;
            two = two + 3;
            three = three + 3;
        }
        one = one + 18;
        two = two + 18;
        three = three + 18;
    }
    return ret;
}

// Maximizes first box, and hides rest. 
async function miniBoxMaximize(num) {
    isMaximizedBool = true;
    document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    // turn off onclick for menu button
    allBoxes[num].style.animation = `${maximizeVars[num]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
    miniBoxOnNumber = num;
    hideRest(allBoxes[num]);
}

// if there is a box enlarged, it will minimize it
function minimizeMiniBox() {
    if (isMaximizedBool) {
        allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber].style.animation = `${minimizeVars[miniBoxOnNumber]} 0.3s ease-out forwards`;
        unHideRest(allBoxes[miniBoxOnNumber]);
        isMaximizedBool = false;
        // turn on onclick for menu button

        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim 3s infinite ease-in-out';
    }
}

// Given a box, hides rest except given box
function hideRest(miniBox) {
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// Given a box, shows rest except given box since given box has its own animation going on
async function unHideRest(miniBox) {
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
    for (let i = 0; i < allBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (!allBoxes[i].isEqualNode(miniBox)) {
            allBoxes[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
        }
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < allLines.length; i++) {
        allLines[i].style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.25s ease-out forwards';
    }
}

// this is for the individual 81 numbers!!
async function clickedTapBox(boxNumber) {
    if (isMaximizedBool && GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[boxNumber] === '0') {  // This ensures that the tap-box number isnt increased by 1 unless the box is maximized
        let theNumber = allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML;
        if (theNumber === '') {
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = 1;
            //GAME_STATE[boxNumber] = '1';
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, '1');
            localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE);
        } else {
            theNumber = parseInt(theNumber);
            if (theNumber === 9) {
                theNumber = '';
            } else {
                theNumber = theNumber + 1;
            }
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.1s ease-out forwards';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 100));
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = theNumber;
            allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
            // save game state
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, theNumber.toString());
            localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
    if (isSolved()) {
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
        minimizeMiniBox();
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 1000));
        skipClicked(1);
    }
}

function isSolved() {
    if (GAME_STATE === hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer']) {
        return true;
    } else {
        return false;
    }
}

// personal replace function
String.prototype.replaceAt = function(index, replacement) {
    return this.substr(0, index) + replacement + this.substr(index + replacement.length);
}

// this will start the game either from where left off or new game
function fillStartingState() {
    for (let i = 0; i < allTapBoxes.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i];
            allTapBoxes[i].style.color = '#545454';
            allTapBoxes[i].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        } else if (GAME_STATE[i] !== '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_STATE[i];
            allTapBoxes[i].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        } else  {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
        }
    }
}

// this needs to happen before the function call below
if (!localStorage.getItem("hardGameNumber")) {
    localStorage.setItem("hardGameNumber", "0");
    localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', hardGames[0]['question']);
} else {
    GAME_NUMBER = localStorage.getItem('hardGameNumber');
    GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    GAME_STATE = localStorage.getItem('hardGameState');
}
setTimeout(fillStartingState, 2700);

async function menuButtonClicked() {
    if (!isMaximizedBool) {
        if (!isMenuOpen) {
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToMenuDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuOpen 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'hidden';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim1 3s infinite ease-in-out';
            isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
        } else {
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowToGameDirection 0.25s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('menu-tray').style.animation = 'menuClose 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.4s forwards ease-in-out';
            document.getElementById('game-box').style.visibility = 'visible';
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 250));
            document.getElementById('tray-button-div').style.animation = 'arrowPulseAnim 3s infinite ease-in-out'; 
            isMenuOpen = !isMenuOpen;
        }
    }
}

// SKIP CURRENT GAME
async function skipClicked(num) {
    if (num === 0) {
        menuButtonClicked();        
    }
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
    GAME_NUMBER = parseInt(GAME_NUMBER);
    if (GAME_NUMBER === 299) {
        GAME_NUMBER = 0;
    } else {
        GAME_NUMBER = GAME_NUMBER + 1;
    }
    GAME_NUMBER = GAME_NUMBER.toString();
    GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    GAME_STATE = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['question'];
    localStorage.setItem("hardGameNumber", GAME_NUMBER);
    localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE);
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';

    // clean up the board
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE.length; i++) {
        allTapBoxes[i].style.color = '#f2ebd3';
        allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
    }

    const miniLinesVertical = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('mini-board-vertical-line'));
    const miniLinesHorizontal = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('mini-board-horizontal-line'));
    const linesVertical = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('board-vertical-line'));
    const linesHorizontal = Array.prototype.slice.call(document.getElementsByClassName('board-horizontal-line'));
    for (let i = 0; i < miniLinesVertical.length; i++) {
        miniLinesVertical[i].style.animation = 'none';
        miniLinesHorizontal[i].style.animation = 'none';
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < linesVertical.length; i++) {
        linesVertical[i].style.animation = 'none';
        linesHorizontal[i].style.animation = 'none';
    }
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
    for (let i = 0; i < miniLinesVertical.length; i++) {
        miniLinesVertical[i].style.animation = '';
        miniLinesHorizontal[i].style.animation = '';
    }
    for (let i = 0; i < linesVertical.length; i++) {
        linesVertical[i].style.animation = '';
        linesHorizontal[i].style.animation = '';
    }
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.2s forwards ease-in-out';
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 2700));
    fillStartingState();
}


// Clears the user input from the board
async function clearInputClicked() {
    menuButtonClicked();
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeOut 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';
    await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 300));
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] === '0') {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = '';
        } else {
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i];
        }
        GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(i, GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i]); // update the game state
    }
    localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE); // update the locally stored variable
    document.getElementById('game-box').style.animation = 'opacityFadeIn 0.3s forwards ease-in-out';
}

async function hintClicked() {
    let emptyPos = [];
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0') {
            emptyPos.push(i);
        }
    }
    if (emptyPos.length > 0) {
        menuButtonClicked();
        await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 400));
        let randomHintIndex = randomInteger(0, emptyPos.length);
        
        let boxNumber = emptyPos[randomHintIndex];

        let theNumber = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer'][boxNumber];
        allTapBoxes[boxNumber].innerHTML = theNumber;
        allTapBoxes[boxNumber].style.animation = 'popBounce 0.2s ease-out forwards';
        GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(boxNumber, theNumber.toString());
        localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE);

        if (isSolved()) {
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 200));
            minimizeMiniBox();
            await new Promise(r => setTimeout(r, 1000));
            skipClicked(1);
        }
    }
}

function randomInteger(min, max) {
    return Math.floor(Math.random() * (max - min)) + min;
  }

  

// THIS FUNCTION IS FOR TESTING PURPOSES ONLY AND SHALL BE REMOVED IN PROD
async function quickSolve() {
    let one = 0;
    for (let i = 0; i < GAME_STATE.length; i++) {
        if (GAME_STATE[i] === '0' && one === 0) {
            one = 1;
        } else if (GAME_ORIGINAL_STATE[i] === '0') {
            let theNumber = hardGames[GAME_NUMBER]['answer'][i];
            allTapBoxes[i].innerHTML = theNumber;
            GAME_STATE = GAME_STATE.replaceAt(i, theNumber.toString());
            localStorage.setItem('hardGameState', GAME_STATE);
        }
    }
}